export const questions = [
  { qid:'qid1', question:'Question#1', answer:'1', choices: [1, 2, 3, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid2', question:'Question#2', answer:'2', choices: [2, 3, 4, 5] }, 
  { qid:'qid3', question:'Question#3', answer:'3', choices: [3, 4, 5, 6] }, 
  { qid:'qid4', question:'Question#4', answer:'4', choices: [4, 5, 6, 7] }, 
  { qid:'qid5', question:'Question#5', answer:'5', choices: [1, 2, 3, 5] }, 
  { qid:'qid6', question:'Question#6', answer:'6', choices: [1, 2, 6, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid7', question:'Question#7', answer:'7', choices: [1, 7, 3, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid8', question:'Question#8', answer:'8', choices: [8, 2, 3, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid9', question:'Question#9', answer:'9', choices: [1, 0, 9, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid10', question:'Question#10', answer:'10', choices: [1, 11, 10, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid11', question:'Question#11', answer:'11', choices: [1, 2, 3, 11] }, 
  { qid:'qid12', question:'Question#12', answer:'12', choices: [1, 2, 12, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid13', question:'Question#13', answer:'13', choices: [1, 2, 13, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid14', question:'Question#14', answer:'14', choices: [1, 2, 3, 14] }, 
  { qid:'qid15', question:'Question#15', answer:'15', choices: [15, 2, 3, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid16', question:'Question#16', answer:'16', choices: [1, 16, 3, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid17', question:'Question#17', answer:'17', choices: [1, 2, 17, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid18', question:'Question#18', answer:'18', choices: [1, 2, 18, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid19', question:'Question#19', answer:'19', choices: [1, 19, 3, 4] }, 
  { qid:'qid20', question:'Question#20', answer:'20', choices: [1, 20, 3, 4] }
]